

PROFILE

A fresh graduate with experience in game development using the Unity engine and C# as a programming language. A multimedia journalist served in the official student publication of BISCAST, The Collegian. Continually learning about this field as well as basic web app development.

SKILLS

- C# and Unity
- .NET 6.0
- SQL Server
- Basics of Google Firebase
- Photo and Video Editing
- · Flexible and goal oriented
- Attention to detail

NOTABLE ACHIEVEMENTS

- Part of the ReDev Team Top 16 Startup Awardee
- President Lister Awardee

DON GUIRUELA

GAME DEVELOPER

+63 938 897 8380



guirueladon@gmail.com



donguiruela.github.io/aficio60

EDUCATION

Bicol State College of Applied Sciences and Technology

BS Entertainment and Multimedia Computing, Aug 2019 - July 2023

- Academic Distinction with GWA 1.43
- Journalism Award
- SEAMEO TVET Virtual Exchange Student Participant Politeknik Jakarta, Indonesia

Homobono H. Gonzalez National High School

With High Honor, Class of 2019

- GWA of 96
- · Academic Excellence in Mathematics, Research and Innovation, Computer Programming, Computer System Servicing NCII

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Game Developer

June 2023 - Present

- Prepare game design ideas
- Code game mechanics into playable systems using C# design patterns and Unity engine
- · Optimize games for specific platform

Multimedia Editor

The Collegian, Aug 2020 - May 2022

- Supervise the Layout Artists in publication's key issues
- Manage all social media platforms of the publication
- · Coordinate video editing and overall production with the broadcasting team

Freelance Developer

Jul 2019 - Aug 2020

- Optimize the system's back-end performance
- · Database migration from XAMPP to SQL Server for optimal database management